<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/Blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/Blog/"/>
  <updated>2015-08-18T10:21:59-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/Blog/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loops]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/Blog/blog/2015/06/29/loops/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-29T10:19:39-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/Blog/blog/2015/06/29/loops</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week I learned a lot!I have progressed a lot in worksheet 2 but there&rsquo;s still a couple thing that i don&rsquo;t completely understand like loops. I also had lots of fun doing our first workshop. Everyone took it seriously and participated. I learned what a scrum board does and how it works. Overall week 3 was good.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript and Mood Boards]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/Blog/blog/2015/06/26/javascript-and-mood-boards/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-26T10:13:07-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/Blog/blog/2015/06/26/javascript-and-mood-boards</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week I have learned a lot! We began learning about Java and a lot of the stuff we learned in chapter one is related to math. This made it very easy to learn because I think that Math is my best subject and I LOVE algebra! It was kind of challenging because we had to solve it by order of operations and there were some in which I didn&rsquo;t know which part I had to do first. We also began doing our mood boards which I found lots of fun! I created my board on pinterest which I already had experience doing. The pictures that I selected to have in my board involved fashion, music, nature, quotes and my family! overall this week went well, but We just started working on chapter 2 of our workbook and i&rsquo;m struggling a bit with it .</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to My Blog]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/Blog/blog/2015/06/19/welcome-to-my-blog/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-19T10:03:53-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/Blog/blog/2015/06/19/welcome-to-my-blog</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I have learned a lot this week! I learned about markdown, pwd, hostname, mkdir, cd, ls, rmdir, touch, cp I have also learned how to install apps on my computer using codes.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
